[wind blowing]
[gentle creaking]
[wind blowing softly]
[soft, unnerving ambient hum]
[intensely grim
and ominous music playing]
[bell tolling]
[ominous rumbling]
[low, throaty breathing nearby]
[wood creaking]
[grim music continues]
[music swells]
[exhales sharply]
[music fades]
[creaking, rustling]
[owl calling]
[birds chittering]
[leaves crunching underfoot]
[twig snaps]
[inhales sharply]
[wings fluttering]
[jarring, rapidly intensifying
ominous music playing]
[music fades]
[crackling]
[shrill instrumentals playing]
[panting]
[tense, menacing music playing]
[grunts]
[music softens to gentle melody]
[birds chittering]
[whistles short
melodic call]
[whistles bird call]
Shh.
[pants softly]
[gasping]
[soft dramatic music playing]
[birds chirping]
[chuckles softly]
[music continues]
[rapid, warbling whistle
in distance]
[high-pitched whistle responds]
[shrill whistle]
[gasps]
[piercing whistle]
[tense, sinister music playing]
[whistles continue]
[shrill whistle]
[grim music playing]
[melodic, lilting whistle]
[whistles continue]
[music intensifies slowly]
[panting]
[tense rhythmic music playing]
[high-pitched whistle
in distance]
[shrill whistle in distance]
[music softens slightly]
[gasps]
[tense, ominous music playing]
[grunts]
[thuds]
[music softens]
[groans, coughs]
[grunts]
[chains rattling]
[clattering]
[soft, shaky breathing]
[whistles single extended note]
[car door closes]
[engine starts]
[woman grunts]
[dark, discordant music playing]
[music fades]
[engines rumbling]
[dramatic instrumentals build]
[dark synth pop music playing]
[breathing rapidly]
[panting]
[chains rattling]
[muffled thumping]
[vehicle slows on gravel]
[brakes squeaking]
[car stops]
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
[chains rattling]
[grunting]
[tree creaking loudly]
[Azrael gasping, whimpering]
[menacing music playing]
[panting]
[objects clattering softly]
[hisses, pants]
[grunts]
[Azrael breathes heavily]
[dark, ominous music playing]
[panting]
[squelching slice]
[gasps, pants]
[music fades]
[exhales deeply]
[wind blows softly]
[items clattering]
[wind howling]
[cacophonous rustling]
[clanking, squeaking]
[creaking loudly]
[grim instrumentals playing]
[shuddering]
[music darkens]
[music fades]
[wind quiets]
[panting]
[clattering gently]
[whimpering softly]
[tinkling softly]
[Azrael whimpers softly]
[ominous note resonates]
[dramatic rumbling note
hits, fades]
[grim, suspenseful music
playing]
[creaking]
[music fades]
[items clattering softly]
[creaking]
[heaving, exaggerated breathing]
[tense, droning music playing]
[leaves rustling, crunching]
[grim, rumbling instrumentals
playing]
[heaving breaths continue]
[panting, whimpering]
[grunting]
[heaving breathing continues]
[grunts]
[panting]
[throaty, growly breathing]
[guttural howling]
[rhythmic heaving breathing]
[wind whistling]
[rhythmic breathing continues]
[creaking]
[creaking, cracking]
[low, raspy growling]
[frantic, heaving breathing]
[dramatic music playing]
[breathing grows more intense,
bark-like]
[creature roaring]
[squelching thud]
[rhythmic breathing quiets]
[gurgles, grunts]
[muted breathing continues
in distance]
[squelching grunt]
[tense music builds slowly]
[snarling shriek]
[rhythmic breathing continues]
[growls]
[panting]
[rhythmic breathing quickens]
[snarling]
[cacophony of rhythmic breathing
and snarling bites]
[cacophony builds]
[cacophony ends abruptly]
[dramatic music playing]
[rhythmic heaving breaths]
[breathing slows, stops]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
[music fades]
[wind whistling]
[rustling]
[water lapping, rushing]
[pattering loudly]
[solemn, dramatic music playing]
[bird chittering]
[panting]
[solemn music continues]
[breathes heavily]
[music fades]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[ominous music playing]
[trees creaking]
[sniffles]
[footsteps thumping]
[leaves rustling]
[creature growling]
[raspy breathing]
[growling softly]
[thuds]
[breathing heavily]
[sniffs, huffs]
[intense dramatic music playing]
[low, raspy growl]
[soft, throaty breathing]
[gasping]
[sniffles]
[music fades]
[solemn music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[sniffles]
[rustling softly]
[glass clinks]
[bird chitters]
[tense music playing]
[glass clinks]
[eerie, suspenseful music
playing]
[leaves crunching softly
underfoot]
[music intensifies slightly]
[crack]
[grunts softly]
[rattles gently]
[music fades]
[wind blowing]
[fire crackling]
[person groans, coughs nearby]
[clanks loudly]
[bottles clinking]
[panting]
[somber music playing]
[short, sharp whistle]
[music darkens]
[panting]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
[music fades]
[person groans nearby]
[coughs]
[woman wheezes]
[wheezes]
[dark, menacing music playing]
[discordant, scratching note
playing]
[door creaking]
[low, throaty breathing]
[door thuds closed]
[creaking]
[overlapping wheezing breaths]
[soft, eerie instrumentals
playing]
[wind whistling]
[metallic squeaking]
[chorus of heavy breathing]
[wind quiets]
[breathing slows, softens]
[door creaking]
[ominous instrumentals drone]
[door creaks]
[door slams shut]
[hisses]
[gasps]
[wood creaks]
[grim music playing]
[wind whistling]
[music fades]
[floor creaks underfoot]
[sinister music playing]
[creaking]
[door creaks open]
[twig snaps softly]
[breathing heavily]
[wood creaks]
[gasps]
[gasping]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[thud]
[panting]
[metal clanking]
[tense music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[metal clanking]
[shrill, piercing whistle]
[whistling]
[clanking]
[short, sharp whistle]
[cacophonous clanking]
[rat whining]
[clanking continues]
[grunting]
[groans]
[music intensifies rapidly]
[gun cocks]
[gunshot echoes]
[music fades]
[sighs]
[panting]
[music fades]
[grim music builds slowly]
[panting]
[gasps, breathes heavily]
[trees creaking softly]
[wind blowing]
[panting]
[leaves crunching nearby]
[sharp, guttural snarl]
[growling]
[twig snaps]
[snarling shriek]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
[creature wailing]
[loud, guttural moaning]
[snarling]
[growling]
[breathing heavily]
[engine idling]
[speaking foreign language]
Huh?
[muffled growl in distance]
[speaking foreign language]
[dramatic music playing]
[pounding]
[speaking foreign language]
[engine revving]
[speaks indistinctly]
[speaking foreign language]
[gentle, dramatic music playing]
[radio beeps]
["Driver's Seat"
by Sniff 'n' the Tears playing]
♪ Doing all right ♪
♪ A little jiving
on a Saturday night ♪
♪ Come what may
♪ Gonna dance the day away ♪
♪ Driver's seat, ooh ♪
♪ Driver's seat, yeah ♪
♪ We're doing all right... ♪
[gunshot]
[gasps]
♪ A little jiving
on a Saturday night, yeah ♪
[gunshot echoes]
[tires screeching]
[loud crash]
[radio distorts, stops]
[air hissing]
[lights crackling]
[radio buzzing]
["Run Away" by I.M.S.
playing faintly]
[Azrael grunts, groans]
["Run Away" continues]
[gasps]
[man coughs, gags nearby]
[leaves crunch underfoot]
[music volume increases]
♪ ...away to search the truth
[grunts]
["Run Away" continues
loudly in foreground]
♪ You can close your eyes... ♪
[gunshot]
[high-pitched ringing]
♪ You can run away
to search the truth ♪
[gun cocks]
[gun clicks]
[hisses]
[grunts]
[groaning]
["Run Away" continues]
[grunts]
♪ Giddy-iddy-up,
go, go, go-go ♪
["Run Away" continues]
[grunting]
[gunshot]
[high-pitched ringing]
[gasping]
["Run Away" continues faintly
from the radio]
♪ You can close your eyes
to see me through ♪
♪ You can run away
to search the truth ♪
[Azrael breathes heavily]
["Run Away" fades]
[breathes heavily]
[eerie music playing]
[trees creaking]
[breathes heavily]
[tense, ominous music playing]
[music fades]
[gasping breaths]
[gasps]
[Azrael breathes heavily]
[dark, ominous music playing]
[groans]
[leaves crunching underfoot]
[music darkens]
[wheezes]
[grunting]
[Azrael screaming hoarsely]
[twigs snapping]
[ominous rumbling]
[wind blowing]
[rustling]
[tense, suspenseful music
playing]
[grunting]
[hissing]
[ominous music builds]
[music drops off suddenly]
[breathes heavily]
[growling]
[screaming hoarsely]
[multiple guttural growls]
[grunts]
[creatures groaning]
[straining]
[snarling]
[gasping]
[squelching]
[screaming hoarsely]
[low, throaty moaning]
[jarring dramatic music playing]
[growling continues]
[music fades]
[creature groaning]
[soft, guttural growling]
[coughs]
[solemn music playing]
[thudding footsteps]
[sharp, piercing snarl]
[rapidly intensifying dramatic
music playing]
[Azrael gasping]
[growls]
[roars]
[music ends suddenly]
[grunts]
[rope creaking]
[coughs]
[wheezing]
[groaning]
[coughing]
[sniffles]
[coughs]
[groaning]
[coughing]
[breathing heavily]
[dramatic music playing]
[intensely grim
and ominous music playing]
[music softens]
[music fades]
[wind blowing]
[whistles single extended note]
[sinister music playing]
[whistles single extended note
in different pitch]
[Azrael whistles
single extended note]
[short, sharp whistle]
[music intensifies slowly,
darkens]
[music softens slightly]
[music intensifies once more]
[breathing softly]
[clattering thud]
[dark, ominous music playing]
[door creaking]
[music builds slowly]
[tense, suspenseful music
playing]
[grunts]
[gunshot]
[metal clanks]
[fabric rips]
[thuds]
[Azrael breathes heavily]
[low, echoing creaking]
[dramatic music playing]
[wind howling]
[soft rhythmic breathing]
[panting]
[wood creaking]
[loud rustling]
[grunting]
[wind howling]
[dark, ominous music playing]
[panting]
[banging]
[hoarse, muted screaming]
[dirt skitters on lid]
[banging continues]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
[dirt skitters softly]
[grunts]
[panting]
[wind whistling]
[liquid trickling]
[clattering]
[rustling]
[wind howling]
[rustling continues]
[breathes heavily]
[liquid pattering softly]
[gasps]
[creature moans softly]
[snarls]
[panting]
[dark, suspenseful music
playing]
[snarls]
[music drops off abruptly]
[creature groans]
[throaty groaning]
[breathes heavily]
[snarling]
[screams hoarsely]
[sniffing]
[tense music playing]
[fabric rips]
[sniffing]
[music intensifies]
[shrill, wheezing snarl]
[music softens]
[creature snorts]
[gasps]
[metallic creaking]
[music fades]
[fire crackling]
[muted, croaky grunting]
[sighs]
[metal squeaking, rattling]
[wind howling]
[dirt rustling]
[grunts]
[slowly intensifying
dramatic music playing]
[music fades]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
[rumbling]
[fire crackling]
[tense, ominous music playing]
[panting]
[grunting]
[clanging]
[overlapping whistles]
[clanging continues]
[gunshot echoes]
[gunshot ricochets]
[gunshots continue]
[rumbling explosion]
[grunts]
[short, sharp whistle]
[music intensifies]
[music softens]
[gasping]
[music fades]
[gunshot ricochets]
[tense, discordant
instrumentals playing]
[gunshot]
[glass shattering]
[shrill, extended whistle]
[gunshot]
[tense music playing]
[short, melodic whistle]
[gunshot]
[shrill, extended whistle]
[high-pitched warbling whistle]
[screams hoarsely]
[metallic clattering]
[gunshot]
[thud]
[gun clicks]
[squelching slash]
[wind howling]
[dark, foreboding organ music
playing]
[music fades]
[grunting]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
[thuds]
[grunting]
[hissing]
[screams mutely]
[splattering]
[woman whimpers]
[eerie music playing]
[gunshot]
[echoing blast]
[gasping]
[shrieks softly]
[dark, dramatic music playing]
[panting]
[grunts]
[tense, suspenseful music
playing]
[music softens]
[sighs]
[groaning]
[grunts, gasps]
[gasps]
[squelching]
[blood pattering]
[baby crying]
[music fades]
[cleaver clatters to floor]
[heavy thud]
[baby crying]
[cries turn harsh, growly]
[grim music playing]
[crying continues]
[low, animal-like wailing]
[music intensifies]
[wailing cries continue]
[music softens once more]
[wind roaring]
[dark, dramatic music playing]
[door thuds]
[baby cries echoing]
[cries echoing loudly]
[wind howling]
[wailing cries continue]
[cries echoing]
[crying continues]
[baby crying]
[intensely grim
and ominous music playing]
[baby crying]
[eerie music playing]
[low, throaty growling]
[snarling softly]
[baby crying]
[tense, suspenseful music
playing]
[roaring]
[bleating cry]
[crying continues]
[dark and slowly intensifying
dramatic music playing]
[chorus of howling roars]
[baby wailing]
[music drops off suddenly
and fades]
[grim, haunting organ music
playing]
[music fades]
[slightly brighter
organ music playing]
[music fades]
[heavy, dramatic organ music
playing]
[chorus of unnerving,
guttural wails]
[music fades]
[low microphone
feedback humming]
[tense note resonating]
[discordant, scratching note
playing]
[dark, ominous music playing]
[rumbling note echoing]
[ominous music continues]
[music intensifies slowly]
[music drops off, fades]
[music ends]
[soft, solemn music playing]
[music fades]